https://www.airberth.com/privacy-policy/

HomeHow it worksBoats we liftCruisingExtreme WatersportsFishingHigh PerfomanceGovernment & CommercialNewsDealersContactPrivacy PolicyAIRBERTH MARKETING PTY LTD respects your privacy and confidentiality as a visitor to this website. This privacy policy outlines how AIRBERTH MARKETING PTY LTD collects and uses the information provided by its visitors. It gives you a peace of mind, should you decide to share any information with AIRBERTH MARKETING PTY LTD.Collection of InformationIf you decide to share any personal information(name, email address, postal address, interests, etc.) with AIRBERTH MARKETING PTY LTD, the information may be stored and used for research purposes, marketing initiatives and correspondence. AIRBERTH MARKETING PTY LTD assures you that your personal information will not be disclosed to any other party, with the exception of distributors, partners, associates, affiliates and agents of AIRBERTH MARKETING PTY LTD; or unless required by the law.AIRBERTH MARKETING PTY LTD may automatically collect anonymous information about visitors to its website, including IP address, referral website(if applicable), and country of origin. This anonymous information will not be used for linking to any of your personal information. The anonymous information is only used to create user profiles and to personalise the website to the visitors’ own interests.Mailing ListIf you have made a request to be notified about the latest updates and promotions from AIRBERTH MARKETING PTY LTD, its distributors, partners, associates, affiliates and agents, you will automatically be on our mailing list. However, if you wish to stop receiving any more updates and promotional material from us, just inform us via e-mail, to have your name removed from the mailing list. Should you change your mind later, you can request for resubscription by sending us an e-mail, at any time.Linked WebsitesAIRBERTH MARKETING PTY LTD is not responsible for the contents, privacy policies and practices of other websites, which are linked from its website, including the websites of its distributors, partners, associates, affiliates and agents. Please refer to the privacy policies and practices of the respective websites.Further QuestionsIf you have further questions or concerns about the content, privacy policy and practices of this website, please contact info@airberth.com.LegalAs a visitor to this website, you agree to all the terms and conditions in this privacy policy; and in the Terms of Use section. AIRBERTH MARKETING PTY LTD reserves the right to modify this privacy policy at any time without prior notice. First Name*Surname*Phone*Email Address* City, State / Province*CountryAbout Your BoatBoat Brand*Boat Model*Tell us more about your boatAdditional information lets us give you a quicker price. Show moreDrive SystemHull LengthBoat BeamHull Weight (Kg)Engine Weight (Kg)Fuel Capacity (L)Water Capacity (L)Holding Tank Capacity (L)Other Weight (Kg)Total Weight (Kg)DeadriseCommentsAdditional Comments
© 2020 AirBerth Marketing PTY LTD. All rights reserved.Terms of UsePrivacy Policy
